HOWARD:
I'm busy too! You answer it!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
I can't! I'm on the toilet!
HOWARD:
God's sake, I don't need to hear that!
Can't you just say, "I'm busy?"
MRS. WOLOWITZ: I said, "I'm busy,"
but that wasn't good enough for you!
HOWARD: I hope it's one
of those home invasion deals...
(Howard:)...and they shoot me in the head.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Well, if it's a home
invader, don't tell them I'm on the toilet!
(Howard:)There's no one there.
(Howard:)You're hearing things,
you crazy old lady.
(Leonard:)Hey, Stuart. Have you seen Sheldon?
(Penny:)Yeah.
He's, uh, over in the graphic novel section.
(Stuart:)Built himself a little nest.
(Penny:)Thank you.
(Stuart:)-Uh, Penny.
-Yeah?
(Stuart:)-Is everything okay?
-What do you mean?
(Stuart:)Uh, Sheldon told me you and Leonard
are having a fight.
Oh, yeah, kind of. It's no big thing.